it's week seven of me turning this $100
into a million now last week was a
little bit crazy because I actually
turned $8,000 into
$22,000 but now the goal for this week
is to actually turn these same
$22,000 into
$44,000 so with that being said let the
challenge
begin well it's Sunday right now so this
would be tomorrow for me for you guys
it' probably be in 2 seconds
good morning ladies and gentlemen
welcome to week number seven turning
$100 into a million so this week's goal
is to turn the $22,000 into $44,000 and
you know what you want to know what's
crazy like as I keep getting closer to
this million right you know as I'm
growing the account people are
constantly like getting closer to me
because they want to be part of now the
big numbers nobody want to be part of
turning the 100 bucks to 200 200 to 400
cuz boring right it's just super boring
but now I'm about to turn this 22 to
about 30 40,000
and look what look what shows up here
huh I'm going to copy the traits so this
guy doesn't know how to trade right he's
like learning how to trade now so I got
to teach him and he wants to look look
at this wallpaper fun number one that's
how you know it's real so even it be
your own people as you start getting up
they just they only come when they need
something remember that it be your own
so come here come here this what I sh
come here bring me the chair get the
chair all right
so okay all right so this is week number
seven turning $100 into a minute so this
is what we do here right we do trade
update what time is it 11:19 11:19
starting balance is
$22,000 right so now this week we have
four solid Market opportunities all
right the first one is going to be gbpn
DD right now where we currently have a
very very strong level of support we
have resistance support level all
throughout here and currently we have a
potential left head right shoulder
obviously if we were to break through
that neckline but this Market structure
is bullish it went bearish higher low
higher high lower low lower and then it
went bearish here then after as soon as
it Clos above this structure it went
bullish and now we're back at this
strong support level if you look at it
on the weekly time frame it looks
absolutely beautiful it is retesting
these w in the structure weekly had a
strong higher high now having high
higher low and we're at the round
psychological level one well 2.200 or
smart money concept right smart money
concept smart money concept smart money
concept or the blocks or the blocks that
he's a smart money concentrator and look
where he is you know that speaks for
itself um
so so daily time frame we are bullish
and we are rejecting off of the support
level so I'm looking for a little
pullback to buy but if we do body close
under I'm going to then continue to wait
for the retest to then sell once we have
the head and shoulders pattern cuz then
the 4H hour will also be bearish as
right now we've had a reaction from this
point waiting for a little pullback to
have a reaction then they take this
trade to the upside next is going to be
nzd JPY we currently have three very
strong weeks of a push now measure the
most recent three 3 weeks of a pullback
the same 3 weeks don't even make up for
35% of the previous 3 weeks push which
shows you that clearly the sellers are
in the market and buyers are nowhere
near stronger than the sellers so this
is a good indication to look to continue
to sell the last 3 weeks can even engulf
the last one week and coincidentally
enough we are also at this structure
level and support and resistance level
then on the daily time frame obviously
you can see major sellers and look how
hard the daily time frame buyers are
struggling at this level of support and
resistance as you can see left is a
veryable level of supports and
resistance all throughout here so I hate
using trend lines once again I hate
using these channels but it does look
clean so we have this upwards channel
that the market is currently moving in
that it's just a visual representation
to show you that the market is having a
bullish pullback for us to enter this
trade we have to wait for the break and
retest to pretty much go on the cells
it's going to be a very clean sale on
this market right here next is going to
be nzd C so again this is a very
valuable lesson and learn this lesson
because this cost me about a year and a
half of just losses to kind of figure
out how to get to this point where I am
now where I'm avoiding these losses all
the time so let me show you so if you
were to look at this trade just in the 4
Hour you can see that the 4 Hour is very
bullish you would see resistance break
retest you would be obviously in
interested in buying if you to look at
basic Market structure level here you're
going to look at something like this and
this right here is pretty clear
indication to buy there's no way you're
going to sell right into this support
level but the mistake that Traders are
doing is that they're not taking account
the higher time frames if you look at
the daily yes daily looks absolutely
beautiful retesting structure retesting
structure retesting structure to then
head to the upside but we are clearly
not rejecting that point right now why
that is because the weekly time frame is
at a higher high notice how this was
creating lower low lower high now we are
bullish with a higher high so you're
essentially buying this Market at this
point right here on the weekly time
frame you're buying at pretty much the
higher high which is what you don't want
to do the weekly time frame can easily
have a deeper retracement to head to the
upside you're only focusing on this
right here when you go to the 4 Hour and
you're not take in account this whole
move that the weekly time frame has done
to just create that minor pullback so I
would consider this on the 4H hour a
fake out to just get some stop losses
then this will shift bearish so then the
weekly time frame has a deeper pullback
there's a very higher level way of
looking at the markets but once you get
it it'll make a lot a lot a lot of sense
next GBP JPY currently same exact thing
as nzd JPY we've had three very strong
weeks of sells three very soft weeks of
pullbacks and then on the daily time
frame we are currently creating what
looks to be a double top formation we're
going to Simply wait for price to break
and retest out of that neckline of the
double top and then in the 4H hour it'll
be a breaking retest out of this
consolidation Zone that we currently
have right now this is very easy very
textbook I'm simply trading with the
trend there's nothing else that I'm
Reinventing the wheel here next AUD JPY
pretty much just the same thing break
and retest out of this consolidation
Zone we've had three very strong weeks
of sells three very slow weeks of a
pullback retesting structure and you may
ask why are you taking the same trade of
that kind of look the same they're all
JPY and the point is one of like one of
them is going to give the cleanest entry
they're all going to have the move cuz
they're all correlated the same or have
a very similar move cuz they're all
correlated the same because of the JPY
so what I do is that I put all of these
different markets together and I simply
take whichever one looks the cleanest
I'm not stuck or biased on GJ or I'm not
stuck or biased on AUD or ND I don't
really give a [__] I actually don't care
at all I care to take which one makes
the most sense and which one is the
cleanest so I'll put all four of them on
my watch list and they're all going to
probably four have the same move because
they literally just did the same move
for the last 2 months having the push
and the pullback so I'm going to wait
for now to see which one has the
cleanest move so a JPY is literally
pretty much the same thing then GBP CHF
is the one where it's a bit interesting
which is where he took it last week so
this one we have a retest of this level
of support and resistance hasn't quite
made it just yet but it can definitely
still daily time frame we are kind of
creating what the double top of GBP JPY
kind of looks like looks very similar at
this neckline point right here so I'm
going to simply be waiting for a
surprise to just confirm to me that
we're breaking out of this area then
I'll enter on the pull back to then sell
and uh that's pretty much it Euro GBP it
won't be ready this week and then Euro
AUD won't be ready this week at all now
I got to teach my new student how to
trade did you pay me already or no let's
see yeah he's not he doesn't he
[Music]
doesn't all right trade
update decided to come on the boat look
look what a look a beautiful day it is
right you have
people jet skis but right now my boat R
out of gas as is a week day not that
many people working [__]
guys [__] you guys cuz we R out of
gas I I have to pull boat the gas
station which is right there
profitable train yeah I need one of
those already yeah you definitely do bro
I have
a my is probably worth more than that
piece of [__] honestly that is not a
piece of [__] I'm
sorry we go we got a long way to go show
them how far this is it's pretty far
show them how far the [__] bridge is
[Music]
look at
view it's nothing like a Miami View and
a Miami problem oh yeah look it's
barefoot oh look you're walking barefoot
yeah dude if I have a [__] pet peeve
dude I can never in my life walk bareo
not even in my house not even from my
bedroom to the bathroom I can notot walk
backr for my life right now can be
back some black feet Bia
see look this is this is what this is
the vibe right here I can totally pay
for that though if you think about it
the sh are cheap compared to the Bugatti
probably doesn't even own a Bugatti no
but the guy doesn't doesn't own that you
going ready I do it one 2
[Music]
3 all right this one to get the
we in the middle of a [__] hurri
right
now h y set [__] for
[Music]
good morning ladies and gentlemen well
technically good afternoon it is
currently 12: in the afternoon right now
yesterday we got home from the boat
super
late took two trades last night late
into London session um not not this kind
of trade so no we didn't we didn't take
this trade last night in London session
I woke up super late I actually woke up
early I woke up like around 9:1 in the
morning and I look I'm looking at the
chge through my phone like this like
half awake with one eye I'm like Oh
Marcus not doing anything I'm not going
to wake up slept a little bit in the
morning caught up on some sleep because
bro this challenge has literally
literally been draining me right cuz I
stay up during London session throughout
the week messes up my sleep schedule on
the weekend and I'm just all over the
place so I finally caught up on some
sleep oh look look look look look look
look another Traer putting up
oh another unprofitable
Trader hello hello how are you welcome
look good this guy always looks fresh I
can hear to take the traits you know we
got no traits let's go back up so trade
update currently let's start off with
GBP nzd so GBP nzd we have obviously
been waiting for a reaction from the
strong level of support to take the
trade to the upside yesterday once we
had this push to the upside I
anticipated for price to have a pull
back into here then have an entry and
truthfully that's where I would be
looking to enter this position right at
this point but I was not active in front
of the charts at 2: in the morning as
you guys can see down here so this
Candlestick at 2: in the morning I was
not interested in taking the trade now I
could be entering the trade but since it
is currently 12:00 in Miami there's no
Market volume so I'm just going to set
and forget and wait for this daily
Candlestick to close in about 4 hours to
see if it closes under this round
psychological level or above and then
I'm going to determine whether I want to
enter the buy or the sell next nzd JPY
we are still in this channel simply
waiting for a breakout out of it to
enter the trade patience is key in
markets at these times GBP CHF still
waiting for price to break on the destru
level to enter a sell might enter a
little highrisk sell now so GBP CHF
basically waiting for a break and read
this under here to sell or might take a
higher risk trade here nzd CAD we're
still monitoring this to see if it
actually has a real reaction from this
point or if it doesn't GBP JPY is
probably my next favorite prayer because
it is confirming that we are in this
very strong consolidation zone right
here and I'm going to be waiting for
price to have a break and retest out of
this consolidation to then enter this
trade very clear level of support very
clear level of resistance break and
retest is going to be key to making
money with this trade it's going to be
super super super simple and then lastly
GBP JPY once again we're having a very
strong level of support here and
resistance waiting for a break and
retest under it's like what I said the
cleanest ones are the JPY which going to
for whichever want to give us the
cleanest move to then enter the position
for this week so as of right now market
update it is currently
1217 not much else we can do other than
set and forget yesterday we went on the
boat so let's see where today takes
us what is
that all right ladies and gentlemen
trade update it is currently
7:13 in the afternoon before we do this
trade update let's take a ginger shot
this is not a
sponsor Ginger sa are made for a
man you know what's funny people might
think I work out I haven't worked out in
like two
weeks that c for right
there all right trade update currently
right now markets are literally exactly
the same GBP and ZD close exactly how I
anticipated with the daily above the
round psychological level and the
supports I'm going to be looking for
entries on this very very very soon on
the 1 hour time frame next nzd JPY still
within this channel daily time frame
close as a dogee at the top of this
resistance this might be the Candlestick
that gives it the strong rejection to
then head to the downside GBP CHF we are
still waiting for this to have the shift
to the downside very nice daily dogee
which looks fantastic GBP JPY we've had
a very strong daily Doge as well waiting
for the break and retest out of this box
to enter the position to the downside
and as of right now as you guys can see
we are currently
at the same balance of $
22,690
so now we're going to go play some
basketball probably hit the gym for the
first time in two three weeks and most
importantly we're going to Walmart you
guys don't understand why it's important
there is three men living in this house
right now we're surviving just off
purely Uber Eats like that is literally
how we're surviving right now we have
dried out the cabinets we've dried out
the freezer we've eaten eating the cat
food I've haven't been to Walmart in
over a year I'm just so passionate I
want to go probably get some stuff and
see where we go from
[Music]
[Applause]
there 100
[Music]
better I get it right
now you
stay no GM two weeks
why yeah you want some of these
good I got to tast it
too zero sugar on these electrolytes no
promo whatever that's dope [__] sugar
right no dude but it's like you got to
get the healthier ones bro you got to
only get pasteurized eggs are brother
we're at
Walmart we got to at least make an
effort
got you
got just no shot you're never going to
do it dude there it goes oh [__] ah ah
it's not the size of the boat it's the
motion in the ocean
only last so
long good morning ladies and
gentlemen touch that touch that what you
guys know about week seven turning $100
into a million I I I thought I had just
reversed on a so I was like oh [__]
currently right now we are up
$4,000 on the trade now I'm not excited
because get to these $44,000 I could
give a [__] I'm excited about the
potential of this trade that we have
taken if you have seen last week series
you saw the loss we avoided on this
position price had the push stop then
push that's what we are anticipating for
this week to come ahead so we avoided
not making any money this week simply
because because we have experience in
the market now let's look at it now so
trade update we are currently up $4,000
on GBP CHF so if you guys saw last
night's trade update I explained that I
was looking to enter a trade right
around this area once we had the retest
to then sell So currently right now GBP
CHF has a very strong double top
formation currently creating right now
very strong bearish move if this trade
hits all the way down here here we'll
[__] sweep 1 to 11 risk to reward
meaning we will take right now we have
35 Lots right so 35 Lots means that it's
$350 per pip so we do $350 per pip times
a take profit of
342 Pips so
$350 time
342 Pips drum roll please
these
$100,000 in one single position the
beauty of this is not this we're going
to get to this no matter what what is
the beauty is how much I'm actually
putting at risk so I'm only putting at
risk so we have 30 pip stop loss so if I
do
$350 per pip times $30 I'm only putting
at risk 50% of the account this is key
to growth so I'm literally risking 50%
to almost 5x the account tell me that's
not a [__] great deal so as of right
now we are currently just waiting for
this position to have a confirmation
body chemist closure in the next 27
minutes under this level of support
right here the other markets like GBP
nzd we avoided this loss last night by
not entering the position here so it's a
beautiful loss avoided and we simply
remove move this market for us being
interested for the Buys so we're not
interested in the buys well not just yet
we got to confirm if this Candlestick is
going to close above or under nzd JPY is
still in this channel heading to the
upside we are just remaining patient we
are in no rush GJ we are still waiting
for price to have the break and retest
under to actually be able to be
interested in this position so still
waiting on that and then nzd CAD we're
just still watching GBP CHF actively
right now is the baby now GBP CHF is
actually something very interesting that
I might have not told you guys before
GBP CHF is actually the pair that made
me my money back in 2020 I was only
trading GBP CHF that was how actually
passed challenge how I got my first
payout it was on juv PCF which is right
around here right around this Market
time over here so get it on I think it's
yeah it's right here it's on the weekly
time frame so back around over here when
this was a very strong resistance level
you you can see the dates down here
right this is all facts 2020 down here
this was at a very strong resistance and
I caught the break and retest out of
that resistance I caught this whole
entire move not just one move but
scalings throughout this whole entire
move I can almost guarantee you if I go
down to the Daily and I go back this far
yeah look at that there's still markups
from that point back then like I would
enter throughout this whole oh look you
can tell that I would mark it up because
there's like little circles and little
dots that's probably like on the 1 hour
time frame Char doesn't go back that far
on the 1 hour but I have not taken a
trade on GBP CHF in a very long time in
2 years so let's see if this can
actually make us some money how it did
back in the day so for now market update
is currently 1034 in the morning and we
are up as of this very moment right now
oh [__] I had a pull back
$2700 so I didn't forget 44 44 4 4 44 44
40 I should actually hit M [__] I don't
give a [__] because we are almost up
$44,000 on the profit for the week
meaning we are about to hit the take
profit for the week exactly as I expect
let me show you guys the trade where it
is right now so once again we're
currently up 41 oh $40,000 right now
earlier about an hour and a half ago it
was right around here and this is
exactly what I explained we need to
price the body close under that
structure point to confirm that we're
going to end the downside now we are
currently approaching this support level
and we are very strongly breaking under
the key here is going to be that we
remain under this so we can have a
little retest to then sell but we have
to come to a decision at that point
should we just close at 40,000 or do we
hold that trade through that pullback
which it could realistically potentially
go back further than this right here why
well because on The Daily time frame if
the daily Candlestick let's say a body
closes like this it can have a retest to
then this structural level here now
that's just going to be a lot bigger
retracement to than this point now we
can then potentially get a little Wick
out that can then go into our take
profits on look look look look my boys
are calling me CU are training yo you're
didn't C GBP THS cuz you didn't want to
but I sent you a signal no bro what do
you mean bro I what do you mean I didn't
catch it you lost that [__] oh yeah you
want a bet you want to face
him text I I sent you that TR yesterday
oh oh you sent me the JT
huh yest yeah right no it's clean I mean
it's going to have a pullback though not
going to lie no it is it is yeah it's
going to have a did you take it no I
didn't take it bro bro what the
[__] yo I just sent you the signal oh so
you send me the signal you don't take it
that sounds like such a guru thing to do
no no I'm I'm in it though I'm
definitely in it five fine was a clean
it was a clean set up yeah it'll have a
pullback and then you should enter on
the
pullback okay all right d
forget sending me the
signal okay so yeah pretty much 4H hour
Candlestick looks very strong very
bearish engulfing can then wait for
little retest as well for then that
structure level right there basically
more of the story all we got to do right
now is set forget just looks so lovely
dude like we're finally like making
some type of decent money like look at
this man
[Music]
LeBron and
Wade we
another want a trade
today where's the
tra we just set
three wins in a
row I know I made it edit it like if I
made it good morning ladies and
gentlemen it's a bit of a late morning
because I thought I would have this
fixed by this time but clearly I don't
So currently right now it is
11:25 in the morning now I am not upset
because the position is indeed back into
around our entry level or where we would
have been a little bit in a draw down
and I say would have been because last
night you know I decided to close the
positions as it was going back into our
entry point cuz I believed it was going
to keep going but when I Clos these
positions on the way to the entry point
the amount of slippage that I have
received is something I've never seen in
my whole entire life and this is a brand
new broker that I just decided to test
out literally this week because I
believe it was going to be the one that
I was going to share with you guys
because they had a really good offering
no commissions pretty much no spread but
I guess I didn't account the slippage
that they would be putting into your
accounts CU this is actually the first
position that I take on this broker on
the challeng just in general and I'm
definitely going to be changing
platforms as of today I'm going to
withdraw all my money and then I'm going
to go to a different one which I
actually know the guys that are behind
it and that they are running it but the
offer wasn't as attractive as the one
that I'm using right now I decided you
know what let me go for the clickbait
and most attractive thing which on once
again it uh that type of offer like what
what is too good to be true it always
ends up never working out exactly what
happened right now the offer was too
good and I simply got caught in this
whole entire slippage movement and I was
brought in by the really great market
conditions cuz I want you guys to have
the best market conditions if you want
to start your own 100 to the mill but
this broker that I'm currently use right
now is not it so I'm going to switch to
this other one next week because it's
it's a lot more corporate fees are a
little bit higher but I can almost
guarante to you this type of stuff will
never happen but I am going to test it
out before you guys even do cuz up to
this point of the challenge I have not
marketed any broker in the whole entire
challenge the previous challenge or my
whole entire trading career I'm very
very very selective I'm very picky how I
would ever want to do this so this next
one we're going to test it out once
again and see how it is but I'm so tired
because this happened last night like at
3:00 4 in the morning and I've been
battling with the teams of the broker to
see how they can fix this I don't even
care about fixing the profits it's not a
big deal it's more of like the the
morals behind this let me show you guys
so this is the trades from last night
gbpchf you guys can clearly see that we
closed out all three positions at the
same exact time one of them is in profit
and then the other got split in half or
whatever and then it was in a loss so
GBP CHF last night I explained if we had
a retest of this level and then a
rejection to the downside we can very
easily continue to head down if not if
we body Clos above we can come back
right into our area of Interest so we
body closed above and as I'm seeing this
body close above and then I'm seeing
this rejection from the EMA but then I
see this retest of this level of support
that every single time we're above we're
clearly heading up I say oh [__] this is
the area where I want to get out cuz I
could get pushed right back into my
entry and I don't want to be in a loss
at this point in the challenge I'm doing
so well so decided to close my position
right at that line right there right at
1.12 282 right at 3:00 in the morning 4:
in the morning which is like when London
session is kicking in you guys can see
down here the times and I closed out the
first position right the 20 Lots so the
20 Lots gave me $2,000 in profit now
we're going to do some calculations
right now because if I enter the
position up at this point right here and
then we close out the position let's say
somewhere in here that is a total of
about 23 Pips but for argument sake
let's say 20 Pips so I am currently
risking
$200 per pip so it's going to be $200
time 20 Pips I'm supposed to be up
$4,000 on that position I'm up $2,000 so
they ate up 50% of my profits but that's
fine you know what high fees I'll take
it whatever not a big deal but then the
other position when I go close it it is
then in a loss why did I take a loss on
the same position that I entered at the
same spot and close at the same spot why
did it close at a loss now this is where
I get very skeptical about these
platforms because it's just so
unnecessary like I just I just don't get
it and this is why I also split my lot
sizes because everybody says oh why
don't you just take 180 lot it's for
this very same exact reason if I were to
take 80 Lots in a position it would
literally have one full slip without
position versus if I split the positions
in half at least I get one and then the
other ones probably have a little bit of
slippage so I I do this because I've
dealt with this [__] before and I've
been dealing it for a very long time but
I do believe this next platform I'm
going to be a lot better because
personally I've I've always had it there
in the back burning these guys have
always mentioned it to me but i' I've
never wanted to pay higher fees but I'm
at the point where I want to pay high
fees but get the best market conditions
so as of right now this is where we are
on the challenge on the account
basically we're pretty much at the same
starting balance for the week GBP CHF I
do believe it could continue to have a
push to the downside on The Daily time
frame we're having a very strong pull
back into this level not what I expected
as that far but did expect it to have
this 4H hour rejection Candlestick and
if we do body Candlestick close under in
the next hour and a half we can very
clearly easily continue to head to the
downside especially if the 1 hour has a
body Candlestick closure under this
higher low because before this was a
lower high lower low lower high lower
low and now we have a higher high next
GBP nzd daily time frame has now closed
very strongly under so we're going to be
waiting for a retest to them sell nzd
JPY is still in this channel we are
currently just waiting for it to have a
break and retest out of it GBP JPY still
in the channel waiting for the break and
retest out of it and then nzd CAD looks
like it's having a pullback but not even
interested and lastly audjpy we are
currently waiting for this break and
read to out
so [__] man I just hate I hate I hate
shady [__] like this cuz I'm doing
everything as legit and as transparent
as I can possibly do it and there's
outside sources that are affecting the
work that I'm putting into this
challenge I'm supposed to be up right
now probably let's say $30,000 even with
the position being closed at that point
but because of the slippage and because
of all that now I get set back so I'm
I'm this is why I don't want to promote
a broker to you guys because I want to
make sure it's good I don't want you
guys to have to deal with this [__] that
I'm dealing with right now I don't want
to have that type of responsibility so
I'm going to try uh the new this new
broker if you know I see some
opportunities this week which I doubt it
or if not as of next week we're going to
start off with a new opportunity as of
right now pretty much at the same
starting balance on the accounts
so bummer bummer bummer bummer look who
we have back
I've had it for a week and a half it
already had to go in for service $40,000
[__] dollar service so took the
unnecessary loss of the slippage from
the broker today and then a $40,000 bill
from the Bugatti but she's
back we always got security with us SP
always why
[Music]
not these young guys out here they
brought Bugatti watch to do some videos
of the Bugatti it's pretty sick it looks
like the back of the Bugatti this size
is the
prim oh what the [__]
[Music]
I just don't understand how he
understands how to do it so
well yo I Lear I learned how to do the
[__] the what the Yeah I learned how
to do the 360 60 I learned this I think
kid in the back huh I think kids in the
back oh they're
tripping all right right
[Music]
there good morning ladies and gentlemen
it is currently 7:55 in in the morning
so usually I don't do trade up this this
early usually I'm looking at the Trad
for my phone on my bed but today I
decided to wake up early and go out on
the boat we got nothing else to do today
it's Friday no trades in the market not
interested on taking a trade at this
time because usually the market slows
down right around 11:00 so I only have
about 3 hours of trading so in order
instead of me just staying here and kind
of doing nothing today I go on the boat
so let me actually show you guys another
loss that we avoided and how this one
simple trick has cost me over $200,000
of and took me about 2 years to figure
out so yesterday we had GP CHF the whole
entire [__] REM move that this
obviously came back then here I was
looking to then potentially enter this
trade again to the downside but
obviously I cannot enter a sell unless
this time frame is bearish clearly right
here you can see lower low lower high
lowerer low cool right right so as of
right now this is the lower high time
frame right here I mean that's the lower
high and then this lower low point is
right here the moment we body close
Above This lower high we then go bullish
we body closed Above So now this goes
bullish as the higher high and then the
higher low moves to this higher low
point this is now the higher low and the
higher high I can't take a trade here
off just a bearish engulfing when this
structure is clearly bullish but you
know what sometimes you can do this on a
different time frame so if you see up
top over here we're going to change now
to the 15 minute time frame usually the
15minute time frame can show you that
shift of structure beforehand I'm just
going to take off this wrist to reward
this so it looks a lot more clear so
this is clearly the
15minute higher low higher high just put
this simple higher low higher high
higher low higher high so this is the
higher low and then this is the higher
high we are supposed to take the trade
the moment we B Candlestick close under
this line right here to confirm a shift
of structure this will then mean that
the 15-minute time frame is now bearish
what happened here the not body kind of
stay close under so there is no shift
structure so we did not take the trade
on the 1 hour this is what it would look
like right there on the structure I
bring back the risk to reward
tool going to spam this button back this
is where we should have entered the
position on this shift of structure on
the 1 hour this is what it looks like
but we did not because there was no
shift of structure so then hence what we
did is we simply avoided this loss
because there was no shif of
structure see how easy it is you have to
have area of Interest well Trend area of
Interest entry signal Shi of structure
so we avoided this loss to Perfection
GBP nzd this is definitely going to be a
trade that is going to be ready for next
week once we have this retest of this
neckline right here this retest of this
neckline is going to be key to continue
selling this Market to end the downside
nzdjpy 4our time frame still in this
bullish Channel we simply have to set
and
forget GBP JPY is now at the top of this
ranging Market oh GP JP there you go
that is one again at the top of this
ranging market and this looks beautiful
on the weekly time frame if it decides
to close just like that doy Candlestick
because then this would be a beautiful
resistance that then we can res like
resist from and then sell to the
downside on this following week and I
simply get a horizontal line from this
point right here and I drag it to the
left it's clearly a very well respect
the level of support and resistance so
this trade will be ready for next week
nzd CAD we had a pretty decent move to
the upside so we technically did miss
this one can't even lie and then AUD JPY
we have not had the breaking retest
under we're currently approaching this
very strong level of support and
resistance and have to wait for that
reaction so as of right
now nothing this is going to be an
amazing week next week I felt as if all
of this week the pairs and the markets
were getting ready for next week and
there's some weeks that are like that
some weeks are going to be slow and
they're going to be prepping for the
next week and you just have to sit on
your hands and not put money at risk
when there's nothing to put money at
risk kind of how I did this week I put
very little bit of money at risk for
obviously a great reward but I think
this week was loading up for next week
so let's check out what's going to
happen next week so we're going to not
go on the boat probably play a little
montage and see where the day takes us
hopefully it doesn't rain it's a
beautiful day as of right now let's hope
it doesn't rain on us out there that
would Prett
[Music]
suck did you not check the weather
before we came out yeah I did I check it
that
way we'll make it to the beach at least
we get to go to Fisher Island have you
ever been no have you been never been no
your experience I see this as a positive
did we not bring one of those portable
chargers we did yeah let's try it let's
try and charge it well here we find
ourselves in the same situation as last
time a broken
[Music]
bat trading is like the beach when a
Trader goes to his office he expects to
then take a tra when a surfer comes to
the beach he expects to Surf a wave but
if Ser goes to the beach and there's no
waves you can't do anything you're not
going to go out there and get risk eaten
by a shark like literally there's no
waves to Surf like right now you can't
do anything if you go to your trading
desk and there's no trades to take you
can't do anything there's no point of
view overexposing risk when there's no
great opportunities in the markets
there's no points of you coming out to
the beach and trying to Surf when
there's no waves now there's a suck that
you had to drive to the beach and you
had to get your surfboard and go through
traffic to get here yes but it's part of
the game does a suck that you have to
wake up early look at the market for 2
hours and then you don't get your entry
signal yes it sucks but it's part of the
game it's the risk reward of the
business that we're involved right now
so days like today where the market
gives us no
opportunities we just come to the beach
s for
[Music]
I need a bigger boat and we do after
this one yeah I said like this is
already like this is the third time this
is the last draw yeah this is the last
straw I'm getting a bigger
bat n for real I'm
getting it's raining after the rain
what comes after the rain buddy what
comes after the
rain a winning trade more rain literally
Miami right here fact Sunny one second
ago and
now yeah now don't bro dude now it's
Shin sh shining all the way over there
I'm ladies and gentlemen we have made it
home so has been an interesting day you
know what I thought it was going to take
you guys through a fun Vlog and it was
going to be a great time not saying it
it wasn't but it just didn't go
according to plan you know we went a
long long way we just went the wrong
[__] way we ended up at the wrong
spot but it is what it is this week has
consisted of a bunch of different
interesting events that have happened so
let's see what next week has ahead for
us for next week we're going to deposit
these $20,000 into this new broker that
I am going to be testing out which I
will be letting you guys know next week
how that broker Works hopefully it's a
lot better than this one uh it's a lot
more corporate it's a lot more
structured and it's a little bit more
expensive fees but I won't have these
slippage which is extremely annoying so
if you guys want to be part of the cause
of me where I Lally share these trades
every single week with my students click
the link in description below I'm going
to literally give you access to my whole
entire course going to give you access
to my private and score Community I'm
going to give you access to my set and
forget strategy which are the markets on
how I can predict these markets every
single week even though this week it
wasn't a profitable week I was able to
predict these Market moves you're going
to get all those three things and the
Sunday swings for life meaning you're
going to get on a live call with me
every single Sunday where we're going to
be able to break down the pairs live
every single week to see what great
opportunities the markets have ahead for
us and you're going to be able to ask me
any questions live that you may want to
have right there you might ask questions
right now in the comments in this
YouTube video probably never read it
there just too many so for everybody
that gets on the lives with me every
single Sunday I can answer them in much
more detail so appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end hopefully next week we can turn
these $20,000 to $40,000 and no
ridiculous events like this week have
happened but I guess the only way to
find out is to see you next week see you
guys